You're not going to believe what happened at The Oak Room.
The Oak Room is a thriller, horror, mystery film directed by Cody Calahan.
During a raging snowstorm, a drifter returns home to the blue-collar bar
located in the remote Canadian town where he was born.
When he offers to settle an old debt with a grizzled bartender by telling him a story, the night's events
quickly spin into a dark tale of mistaken identities, double-crosses and shocking violence.
Steve, played by RJ Mitte.
Paul, played by Peter Outerbridge.
Michael, played by Ari Millen.
Gordon, played by Nicholas Campbell.
Richard, played by Martin Roach.
Kenneth, played by David Ferry.
The Oak Room is a 2020 Canadian thriller film directed by Cody Calahan, produced by Citizen Skull Productions, and
starring RJ Mitte, Ari Millen, Martin Roach, Nicholas Campbell, David Ferry and Peter Outerbridge.
It is based on Peter Genoway's play of the same name.
The film explores themes of small town, canada, snowstorm, bartender, debt.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.